{
  "answers" : {
    "-KVC38srRqQsaHgWtqNS" : {
      "answer" : "They need to do way instain mother> who kill thier babbys. becuse these babby cant frigth back? it was on the news this mroing a mother in ar who had kill her three kids. they are taking the three babby back to new york too lady to rest my pary are with the father who lost his children ; i am truley sorry for your lots",
      "author" : "Lady Geologist",
      "question" : "-KVC32at1fZzWmVMYe_W"
    },
    "-KVC3HCMiXvOqfMkIIQ4" : {
      "answer" : "A babby is born when you put a tomato and a baby blanket in a blender and stick said blender in the washing machine with more tomatoes. After you are done contemplating your poor life decisions the babby should magically poof into existence the following week at the most awkward time imaginable.Good luck with that!",
      "author" : "April",
      "question" : "-KVC32at1fZzWmVMYe_W"
    },
    "-KVC3NEhUEL4HuYpxxaZ" : {
      "answer" : "Babby is alwez bin babby, babby loafs ye",
      "author" : "Tyrone",
      "question" : "-KVC32at1fZzWmVMYe_W"
    },
    "-KVC3ofALXQTarznwu45" : {
      "answer" : "2010",
      "author" : "coyspurs",
      "question" : "-KVC3l23syMoP_1VEkPR"
    },
    "-KVC3t-PMC0iWFxSlEIQ" : {
      "answer" : "See almost all said 2008- 2010.. Now.. :) why is that? I can answer.. We have awoken to a world that we now know most of us that is fake.. we are in fact in a simulation and so the factor of sleep is null now.. Also other factors will give way as we learn this and a system wide reset will be coming... it may come in the form of the Alein invasion.. it may be WWIII it could come as anything.. be alert stay awake. \n\nA reset doesn't mean anything bad it just means being put back to sleep and you will have ignorance once again to the system. To those of us who can't be we are set free and are no longer part of \"their\" system.. we no longer fit their matrix their scheme.. so we are useless and set free to do nothing.. or to make the choice to free others to free you.. from your prison, of the mind. \nA test is all that is needed.. Here is one. It requires nothing. One day out of any day.. take a whole day to yourself and try this. \n\nRelax think deeply think of all the things in your life that are bothering you.. take them and now toss them out.. See past them. What is it that you are doing really? \n\nAsk the question.. What is this place? Why are you here? how did you get to be here? \nhow did any of us? You'll soon see that doing this results in the system reacting to your thoughts putting doubt into your mind.. putting obstacles in your way where there were none before.. people will shout curse at you for no reason stomp on and at the ground at you.. things.. won't seem normal now will they.. and why? because you are seeing through the looking glass. Seeing a world without you and it is mad.. Mad world. Look up the song listen to it fully understand it and you will cry .. you will then see what this is for what it is.",
      "author" : "anonymous",
      "question" : "-KVC3l23syMoP_1VEkPR"
    },
    "-KVC3yN-mjW2RThq9bJi" : {
      "answer" : "I'm the deepest sleeper ever. I have to have 2 alarms in the morning to wake me up because 1 isn't loud enough. The best night sleep I've ever had was last Saturday in a motel. Damn, that bed was comfortable.",
      "author" : "anonymous",
      "question" : "-KVC3l23syMoP_1VEkPR"
    },
    "-KVC4L9hww8zRVl-l_E-" : {
      "answer" : "No",
      "author" : "anonymous",
      "question" : "-KVC4IiKxZK-qyB1X7uz"
    },
    "-KVC4OPAS27_CAKAMaB6" : {
      "answer" : "Yes",
      "author" : "highpriestess",
      "question" : "-KVC4IiKxZK-qyB1X7uz"
    },
    "-KVC4RNfCeNGTnCZ1Gi5" : {
      "answer" : "I prefer nachos",
      "author" : "nachomanrandysavage",
      "question" : "-KVC4IiKxZK-qyB1X7uz"
    },
    "-KVC4ffV5-s-LBRtbR4F" : {
      "answer" : "Please stop with the cat pictures, Janice. The server can probably handle it, but I can't.",
      "author" : "anonymous",
      "question" : "-KVC4_ze5FWz_yt9bUFI"
    },
    "-KVCC9MJMAKADBwgawO-" : {
      "answer" : "asdf",
      "author" : "anonymous",
      "question" : "-KVC4_ze5FWz_yt9bUFI"
    }
  },
  "questions" : {
    "-KVC32at1fZzWmVMYe_W" : {
      "answers" : {
        "-KVC38srRqQsaHgWtqNS" : true,
        "-KVC3HCMiXvOqfMkIIQ4" : true,
        "-KVC3NEhUEL4HuYpxxaZ" : true
      },
      "author" : "warhammer40k",
      "notes" : "how is babby formed \nhow girl get pragnent",
      "question" : "How is babby formed?"
    },
    "-KVC3l23syMoP_1VEkPR" : {
      "answers" : {
        "-KVC3ofALXQTarznwu45" : true,
        "-KVC3t-PMC0iWFxSlEIQ" : true,
        "-KVC3yN-mjW2RThq9bJi" : true
      },
      "author" : "hollypaw",
      "notes" : "I tend to toss and turn at night, and I'm wondering how normal my experience is.",
      "question" : "When was the last time you had a peaceful sleep?"
    },
    "-KVC47ZTh49jdgSIJq3Q" : {
      "author" : "somemeanie",
      "notes" : "I like to judge people as they walk by my apartment. Is that mean?",
      "question" : "Do you care if people judge you?"
    },
    "-KVC4IiKxZK-qyB1X7uz" : {
      "answers" : {
        "-KVC4L9hww8zRVl-l_E-" : true,
        "-KVC4OPAS27_CAKAMaB6" : true,
        "-KVC4RNfCeNGTnCZ1Gi5" : true
      },
      "author" : "hotdogfan",
      "notes" : "They're generally cheaper than hamburgers, and I'd like my family to stop eating so many hamburgers! Help me convince them that hotdogs are better.",
      "question" : "Do you like hot-dog?"
    },
    "-KVC4_ze5FWz_yt9bUFI" : {
      "answers" : {
        "-KVC4ffV5-s-LBRtbR4F" : true,
        "-KVCC9MJMAKADBwgawO-" : true
      },
      "author" : "janice",
      "notes" : "I want more, but I'm afraid the weight of the cats with crash the server.",
      "question" : "How many cat pictures can I put on my blog?"
    }
  }
}
